# RAHUL DARJI

SENIOR FRONTEND ENGINEER

# CONTACT

+91-9664083586

DARJI.RAHUL316@GMAIL.COM

RDARZ.GITHUB.IO

## **PROFILE**

Experience building products for desktop and mobile app users, meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

# SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS, SASS/LESS, CSS in JS
- Javascript, Jquery, ES6
- React, React-Native, Redux, Redux-thunk, Angular 1
- NodeJs, Express, Loopback
- Template engines Jade, EJS, Nunjucks, Swig
- MongoDB, MySql
- Webpack, Gulp
- Git, SVN
- Web application, Mobile application, Hybrid application, Progressive web apps
- CI/CD integration

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **SENIOR PRODUCT ENGINEER**

SERVIFY, MUMBAI | MAR 2018 - PRESENT

- Created internal system for white labeled app to onboarding new partners using React and redux.
- Implemented higher order components for conditional rendering of role based feature module.
- Provided solution and implemented internationalisation in consumer facing web app.
- Setup configuration to make build with multiple endpoints and also integrated CICD for deployments.
- Developed web view to integrate in third-party app for claim raising flow which is a part of Servify app who provides warranty and protection plan management system.
- Designed mobile app in react-native to provide protection plan and fulfilment with subscription module, cart module and payment gateway integration.
- Worked directly with product management, quality and design engineering to address customer concerns and identify potential product improvements
- Managed continuous improvement projects

#### **WEB ENGINEER**

BUILT.IO, MUMBAI | JAN 2015 - MAR 2018

- Analysed requirements and designed, developed and implemented software applications for multiple websites
- Tested websites and performed troubleshooting prior to deployment
- Took concepts and produced design mock-ups and prototypes to strengthen designs, enhance user experiences and improve site interactions

# **EDUCATION**

### MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI | 2012 - 2015

## **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION**

UNIVERSITY OF PUNEI | 2008 - 2011

## **MASTER OF COMMERCE**

UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI | 2008 - 2011